[
  {
    "index": 0,
    "question": "The sun is setting next door...",
    "answer": "Terrible",
    "description": "It's terrible when the sun goes down next to us"
  },
  {
    "index": 1,
    "question": "Galang keeps books in...",
    "answer": "Ma'am",
    "description": "The book was borrowed by Galang yesterday afternoon."
  },
  {
    "index": 2,
    "question": "United we stand, divided we——-",
    "answer": "Sad",
    "description": "Who doesn't feel sad about divorce from his wife??"
  },
  {
    "index": 3,
    "question": "Food wrapped in banana leaves?",
    "answer": "Lontong",
    "description": "Easy, right? Do you like rice cake?"
  },
  {
    "index": 4,
    "question": "If you drive a car you must bring it",
    "answer": "One",
    "description": "If you bring 2, how do you ride it"
  },
  {
    "index": 5,
    "question": "All jasmine roses...",
    "answer": "Flowers",
    "description": "If not flowers, what are you trying to do, animals?"
  },
  {
    "index": 6,
    "question": "Don't throw the tissue in...",
    "answer": "The place",
    "description": "Still where it was dumped"
  },
  {
    "index": 7,
    "question": "When _____ people usually eat.",
    "answer": "Angry",
    "description": "If people are angry or not, they must eat."
  },
  {
    "index": 8,
    "question": "Birds are animals that can...",
    "answer": "Dude",
    "description": "You fly together with your friends, right?"
  },
  {
    "index": 9,
    "question": "Animals that like to open their mouths wide",
    "answer": "Get the flu",
    "description": "That's because he can't breathe his nose is blocked."
  },
  {
    "index": 10,
    "question": "Animals that change color when there is an enemy?",
    "answer": "Stunned",
    "description": "Because, the enemy stares at the animal changing color"
  },
  {
    "index": 11,
    "question": "A female artist with a thin mustache",
    "answer": "Ihkumisan",
    "description": "Why do you have a mustache?"
  },
  {
    "index": 12,
    "question": "Ordinary door at...",
    "answer": "Press",
    "description": "If you usually keep your pin pressed"
  },
  {
    "index": 13,
    "question": "Lebak Bulus",
    "answer": "Famous",
    "description": "Because of lebak bulus, everyone knows that it's so famous"
  },
  {
    "index": 14,
    "question": "A bullfighter can be injured by being rammed...",
    "answer": "Bicity",
    "description": "If you want a bull, you want a city bus, you can still get hurt."
  },
  {
    "index": 15,
    "question": "Mirror if you wipe it so...",
    "answer": "Mirror",
    "description": "Yes times change, yes always mirror"
  },
  {
    "index": 16,
    "question": "Batik is the original product of...",
    "answer": "Human",
    "description": "So far no other creature has been able to"
  },
  {
    "index": 17,
    "question": "The vehicle that motorcycle taxi drivers like to use?",
    "answer": "Strike",
    "description": "Motor always breaks down"
  },
  {
    "index": 18,
    "question": "What animal can't move?",
    "answer": "Pope",
    "description": "If the game is on whale(e) it will stop playing"
  },
  {
    "index": 19,
    "question": "After exercise",
    "answer": "Drinking water",
    "description": "After exercise, you must be thirsty, right"
  },
  {
    "index": 20,
    "question": "In the wind flutters in every country",
    "answer": "Clothes",
    "description": "In every country people dry their clothes"
  },
  {
    "index": 21,
    "question": "If you are thirsty to drink",
    "answer": "No",
    "description": "Just drink it or it won't wear out"
  },
  {
    "index": 22,
    "question": "What makes you smell good",
    "answer": "Pffffht",
    "description": "It sounds like air freshener pffht"
  },
  {
    "index": 23,
    "question": "Hayam Wuruk rules the kingdom?",
    "answer": "Jamandu",
    "description": "Yeah yeah… the present day"
  },
  {
    "index": 24,
    "question": "What is the most beautiful night?",
    "answer": "Your badge",
    "description": "Eaa…eaa…eaa.."
  },
  {
    "index": 25,
    "question": "Indonesian specialties made from soybeans that have been worldwide",
    "answer": "Delicious",
    "description": "Delicious and nutritious tempeh indeed"
  },
  {
    "index": 26,
    "question": "Animals live in the fields",
    "answer": "Stubborn",
    "description": "The leech lives in the river and likes to suck people's blood. Yes, he has a stubborn name"
  },
  {
    "index": 27,
    "question": "Food must be in...",
    "answer": "Cook",
    "description": "Try to eat uncooked rice"
  },
  {
    "index": 28,
    "question": "Capital of Indonesia",
    "answer": "Udahada",
    "description": "The one that doesn't exist yet is the capital city of Jakarta"
  },
  {
    "index": 29,
    "question": "In palembang there is a bridge..",
    "answer": "drop",
    "description": "It's just a bridge, it can be damaged."
  },
  {
    "index": 30,
    "question": "People exercise so ...",
    "answer": "Inlah",
    "description": "Don't stop if people want to be healthy.."
  },
  {
    "index": 31,
    "question": "Mother sewed with a needle and...",
    "answer": "Seriously",
    "description": "You have to be serious, let's finish..."
  },
  {
    "index": 32,
    "question": "Words to greet the Batak people in the field",
    "answer": "Hello",
    "description": "If you don't reply, it means you're busy, sis"
  },
  {
    "index": 33,
    "question": "The iron bird is also called...",
    "answer": "Order",
    "description": "The one who ordered the bird. asked to be made of iron"
  },
  {
    "index": 34,
    "question": "What shape is the well?",
    "answer": "Hole",
    "description": "Surely a hole without a hole is not a well"
  },
  {
    "index": 35,
    "question": "Signs when a cat is angry the tail?",
    "answer": "One",
    "description": "Because if it's not one it's not a cat"
  },
  {
    "index": 36,
    "question": "What fruit do you often bring when you play at your boyfriend's house?",
    "answer": "Apple",
    "description": "Yes, when you go to your boyfriend's house, you often talk."
  },
  {
    "index": 37,
    "question": "People keep clothes in...",
    "answer": "Any",
    "description": "My mother would have kept it in the closet, if other people knew where.."
  },
  {
    "index": 38,
    "question": "What fruits are old",
    "answer": "cassava",
    "description": "How is the vrohh si – ngkong"
  },
  {
    "index": 39,
    "question": "Not good at studying",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "description": "You can't study smart, you can't study it"
  },
  {
    "index": 40,
    "question": "Animal with a big name",
    "answer": "Fat",
    "description": "Because big animals are fat"
  },
  {
    "index": 41,
    "question": "At the end of the story..",
    "answer": "Tdana",
    "description": "Really? There are letters t and a"
  },
  {
    "index": 42,
    "question": "Elementary is a school",
    "answer": "Peace",
    "description": "May all schools be peaceful, students achieve"
  },
  {
    "index": 43,
    "question": "If thirsty drink",
    "answer": "Cook",
    "description": "The food is not cooked yet, so it has to be cooked first"
  },
  {
    "index": 44,
    "question": "Put a flag on...",
    "answer": "Pull",
    "description": "If you don't pull it, you don't raise the flag"
  },
  {
    "index": 45,
    "question": "The road is wide you can't pass",
    "answer": "Spit",
    "description": "I've tried it myself, it's hard..."
  },
  {
    "index": 46,
    "question": "Before drinking coffee in",
    "answer": "Mouth",
    "description": "Before drinking it must be put in the mouth"
  },
  {
    "index": 47,
    "question": "Nobita's friend..",
    "answer": "A little",
    "description": "Just count how many there are, won't they?"
  },
  {
    "index": 48,
    "question": "Let's take a shower...",
    "answer": "Byuur",
    "description": "Segeerr, have you showered yet?"
  },
  {
    "index": 49,
    "question": "The Jakarta Monument",
    "answer": "Hard",
    "description": "Try not to bite"
  },
  {
    "index": 50,
    "question": "What chicken is so big?",
    "answer": "Universe Chicken",
    "description": "That's really big!"
  },
  {
    "index": 51,
    "question": "wind instruments..",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "description": "Indeed, there are many types, you know."
  },
  {
    "index": 52,
    "question": "Not allowed in the library...",
    "answer": "wash",
    "description": "Then the book will be all wet please..."
  },
  {
    "index": 53,
    "question": "Rizky Febian was born in",
    "answer": "carry",
    "description": "Yes, in the arms first, the period is immediately bathed"
  },
  {
    "index": 54,
    "question": "The fighters against the invaders with weapons???"
    "answer": "Make it yourself",
    "description": "If you don't make it yourself, then who makes it"
  },
  {
    "index": 55,
    "question": "Brother takes my sister to school",
    "answer": "Tired",
    "description": "Carry her in her arms"
  },
  {
    "index": 56,
    "question": "Sick people drink?",
    "answer": "Oi",
    "description": "I'm sick of drinking a lot, I'll get better soon"
  },
  {
    "index": 57,
    "question": "Airplane lands on...",
    "answer": "Help",
    "description": "Pilot, co-pilot, airport operator and others..."
  },
  {
    "index": 58,
    "question": "There is a sister at home",
    "answer": "Cook",
    "description": "Hmm, guess what else to cook..."
  },
  {
    "index": 59,
    "question": "Vehicle A's license plate is from?",
    "answer": "Samsat",
    "description": "Because Samsat is an institution that has the right to issue license plates for motorized vehicles..."
  },
  {
    "index": 60,
    "question": "Heavy rain makes ...",
    "answer": "Wet",
    "description": "If it's hot, it's dry"
  },
  {
    "index": 61,
    "question": "It is recommended to eat with hands...",
    "correct answer",
    "description": "You can do left or right, right is better"
  },
  {
    "index": 62,
    "question": "What not to take on the plane",
    "answer": "Alone",
    "description": "Because if we carry it ourselves it will fall"
  },
  {
    "index": 63,
    "question": "Avocados",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "description": "It can be called"
  },
  {
    "index": 64,
    "question": "Ex-girlfriend called",
    "answer": "No",
    "description": "Today's angry girlfriend"
  },
  {
    "index": 65,
    "question": "In the aquarium there are 10 dead 2 fish left",
    "answer": "Discarded",
    "description": "If you don't throw it away, the other fish will die too"
  },
  {
    "index": 66,
    "question": "Not coming to work because of the day..",
    "answer": "Diphk",
    "description": "Yes, the day you are laid off, you don't have to come to work again."
  },
  {
    "index": 67,
    "question": "Tinky winky",
    "answer": "Absolutely",
    "description": "The names are well-known throughout the world"
  },
  {
    "index": 68,
    "question": "The lizard fell into...",
    "answer": "Smack",
    "description": "I was stabbed and fell"
  },
  {
    "index": 69,
    "question": "Your mouth……..",
    "answer": "Only one",
    "description": "You only have one mouth"
  },
  {
    "index": 70,
    "question": "What causes thirst during Ramadan",
    "answer": "Weather",
    "description": "If it's hot, it will make you thirsty, if you're fasting, you'll be hungry too..."
  },
  {
    "index": 71,
    "question": "Send money via atm?",
    "answer": "Thanks",
    "description": "Thanks for accepting"
  },
  {
    "index": 72,
    "question": "Birds fly with?",
    "answer": "As you wish",
    "description": "Yes, when the cat flies.."
  },
  {
    "index": 73,
    "question": "There is a shrimp behind...",
    "answer": "Gnadu",
    "description": "That's a fact"
  },
  {
    "index": 74,
    "question": "What ice ice can walk",
    "answer": "escalator",
    "description": "If it doesn't work, it's not ice calator but calator ladder"
  },
  {
    "index": 75,
    "question": "The heart is happy even though it doesn't have one",
    "answer": "Glass",
    "description": "Glass isn't that important either"
  },
  {
    "index": 76,
    "question": "Husband, bu sub-district head?",
    "answer": "male",
    "description": "Because if you're not a lesbian, it's a sin..."
  },
  {
    "index": 77,
    "question": "Don't know then don't",
    "answer": "Invite",
    "description": "People who don't know how to cook are invited"
  },
  {
    "index": 78,
    "question": "Animals that howl at night...",
    "answer": "Trapped on",
    "description": "Poor foot was stepped on"
  },
  {
    "index": 79,
    "question": "Fire is held feels?",
    "answer": "Difficult",
    "description": "Fire is hard to hold"
  },
  {
    "index": 80,
    "question": "In the game of badminton",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "description": "Try watching badminton for sure the Indonesian name is shortened"
  },
  {
    "index": 81,
    "question": "There are bolsters there are...",
    "answer": "Thread",
    "description": "What do you use if you don't have a sewing thread?"
  },
  {
    "index": 82,
    "question": "Andi is soaking wet because of?",
    "answer": "Husen",
    "description": "Because Husen threw him into the pool, he's really naughty..."
  },
  {
    "index": 83,
    "question": "Sunset day begins",
    "answer": "Home",
    "description": "It's late if you don't come home, the day will be looking for his mother"
  },
  {
    "index": 84,
    "question": "In order to clean we take a bath with ..........",
    "answer": "Sure",
    "description": "If you're not sure, it's better not to take a shower……."
  },
  {
    "index": 85,
    "question": "People walking on water do not wear",
    "answer": "brain",
    "description": "You know there is a road, why do you have to walk on water"
  },
  {
    "index": 86,
    "question": "A child learns to...",
    "answer": "Kanaja",
    "description": "If you get banned, you won't be smart"
  },
  {
    "index": 87,
    "question": "Animals that eat anything?",
    "answer": "Greedy",
    "description": "Everything eaten"
  },
  {
    "index": 88,
    "question": "Birds fly using..",
    "answer": "spirit",
    "description": "If you're not in the mood, you'll be weak."
  },
  {
    "index": 89,
    "question": "Buy a lamp usually at",
    "answer": "Try",
    "description": "If you buy a lamp, try it first"
  },
  {
    "index": 90,
    "question": "Don't make friends with people",
    "answer": "Missing",
    "description": "How do you do it..."
  },
  {
    "index": 91,
    "question": "People crossing rivers are usually built...",
    "answer": "Run",
    "description": "People don't use roads to cross"
  },
  {
    "index": 92,
    "question": "When are you usually hungry?",
    "answer": "lazy",
    "description": "Because you don't have the energy you get lazy"
  },
  {
    "index": 93,
    "question": "Diligent base...",
    "answer": "Have",
    "description": "If you don't work hard, you won't get results"
  },
  {
    "index": 94,
    "question": "State-owned enterprises can be abbreviated ...",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "description": "Could it be shortened?"
  },
  {
    "index": 95,
    "question": "Tiles were made because",
    "answer": "Need",
    "description": "If you don't need it, why make a tile"
  },
  {
    "index": 96,
    "question": "Answer correctly. this world consists of five ...",
    "correct answer",
    "description": "I told you to answer correctly"
  },
  {
    "index": 97,
    "question": "If you want to take the train usually at...",
    "answer": "Antherin",
    "description": "It's okay to take them to the station, whether it's bringing relatives, friends, or motorcycle taxi drivers."
  },
  {
    "index": 98,
    "question": "Brush your teeth before ?",
    "answer": "Destroyed",
    "description": "When it's broken it's hard to rub"
  },
  {
    "index": 99,
    "question": "People are confused about thinking",
    "answer": "Very long",
    "description": "Yeah..just like you"
  },
  {
    "index": 100,
    "question": "cockroach",
    "answer": "Different",
    "description": "If you call it the same thing, ants..ants..ants.."
  },
  {
    "index": 101,
    "question": "Indonesia's first president",
    "answer": "One",
    "description": "It's definitely one"
  },
  {
    "index": 102,
    "question": "People used to send letters in...",
    "answer": "Pocket",
    "description": "Bagged first, then to the post office"
  },
  {
    "index": 103,
    "question": "The difference between a goat and a sheep",
    "answer": "A little",
    "description": "It's just different feathers"
  },
  {
    "index": 104,
    "question": "Assembling upstream",
    "answer": "River",
    "description": "Actually can go to the lake, but I still want the river.."
  },
  {
    "index": 105,
    "question": "Sport makes the body...",
    "wrong answer",
    "description": "Yes, when exercise makes the body, it's wrong!!"
  },
  {
    "index": 106,
    "question": "The first to discover America",
    "answer": "Not me",
    "description": "Yeah, it wasn't me, the one who found it was Columbus."
  },
  {
    "index": 107,
    "question": "What a sad night",
    "answer": "Night",
    "description": "Yeah, like you..don't be sad…puk..puk.."
  },
  {
    "index": 108,
    "question": "One plus one..",
    "answer": "Two",
    "description": "That's just how hard it is.."
  },
  {
    "index": 109,
    "question": "High school is a high school..",
    "answer": "Safe",
    "description": "If it's not safe, it's not a school.."
  },
  {
    "index": 110,
    "question": "What do people do when they are sick?",
    "answer": "Home",
    "description": "It's true that you're going home.. you're still sick, what's going on.."
  },
  {
    "index": 111,
    "question": "Who likes to eat bananas?",
    "answer": "Many",
    "description": "Not only monkeys like it, some of you like it, right?"
  },
  {
    "index": 112,
    "question": "We are not obliged to buy before Eid?",
    "answer": "Nails",
    "description": "Why buy nails instead of clothes"
  },
  {
    "index": 113,
    "question": "Which bone is blue, come on...",
    "answer": "Tulangit",
    "description": "It's blue right"
  },
  {
    "index": 114,
    "question": "Before flying usually the pilot..",
    "answer": "Goodbye",
    "description": "Let's not look for it like that."
  },
  {
    "index": 115,
    "question": "Friends who are hard to find are normal again",
    "answer": "Pdkt",
    "description": "Cieee eee cieee"
  },
  {
    "index": 116,
    "question": "Turtle flipped?",
    "answer": "Poor",
    "description": "I'm sorry I won't come back later"
  },
  {
    "index": 117,
    "question": "Ten plus six equals six……",
    "wrong answer",
    "description": "Ten plus six by six"
  },
  {
    "index": 118,
    "question": "The car can't go forward because...",
    "answer": "Parking",
    "description": "What are you doing with the car parked in advance"
  },
  {
    "index": 119,
    "question": "Repeated animal name...",
    "answer": "rarely",
    "description": "Rarely try to mention..."
  },
  {
    "index": 120,
    "question": "Running makes",
    "wrong answer",
    "description": "Run ya run, make ya make.."
  },
  {
    "index": 121,
    "question": "What eggs are often afraid of...",
    "answer": "Telorasin",
    "description": "Look at that tattoo, it's scary,"
  },
  {
    "index": 122,
    "question": "What is available at the Padang restaurant",
    "answer": "Money",
    "description": "Let's have a change right.."
  },
  {
    "index": 123,
    "question": "Indonesia is a country with land?",
    "answer": "Airbeta",
    "description": "Independant.."
  },
  {
    "index": 124,
    "question": "Not found",
    "answer": "Stolen",
    "description": "Thieves are insolent"
  },
  {
    "index": 125,
    "question": "Those who break the fast",
    "answer": "Adhan",
    "description": "I thought it was the evening call to prayer, but it's still midday"
  },
  {
    "index": 126,
    "question": "Animals in the zoo",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "description": "It's true that the animals are in the zoo"
  },
  {
    "index": 127,
    "question": "What is the function of the brake?",
    "answer": "Speed",
    "description": "Try it if you don't have brakes. How dare you go fast?"
  },
  {
    "index": 128,
    "question": "One ancestor of mine",
    "answer": "Coach",
    "description": "That's my grandmother, so it's up to me."
  },
  {
    "index": 129,
    "question": "The water that comes down from the sky is called?",
    "answer": "Great",
    "description": "It's great that rain can fall from the sky"
  },
  {
    "index": 130,
    "question": "Measurement of voltage",
    "answer": "Wow",
    "description": "Well, if you shout waaw loudly, it means the tension is high."
  },
  {
    "index": 131,
    "question": "Animal jumps",
    "answer": "Shock",
    "description": "If an animal suddenly jumps, it will be a shock"
  },
  {
    "index": 132,
    "question": "Motorcycles can run because the wheels are shaped ...",
    "answer": "normal",
    "description": "If it's not normal, it's a cube-shaped wheel, isn't it."
  },
  {
    "index": 133,
    "question": "What habits do angkot drivers often do?",
    "answer": "Pull",
    "description": "If you don't take your wife and children, what do you eat?"
  },
  {
    "index": 134,
    "question": "If not, where is the name",
    "answer": "mate",
    "description": "Ciye, if you are in a mate, you won't go anywhere"
  },
  {
    "index": 135,
    "question": "Sweet potatoes & cassava are usually grown in...,"
    "answer": "Grave",
    "description": "Can be harvested at 6-8 months old"
  },
  {
    "index": 136,
    "question": "Newspapers are called letters……",
    "wrong answer",
    "description": "How come the newspaper ..."
  },
  {
    "index": 137,
    "question": "The person who helps use seat belts and serves us on the plane is called...",
    "answer": "Good people",
    "description": "Yes, he's a good person, he likes to help."
  },
  {
    "index": 138,
    "question": "Animals in groups",
    "answer": "hot",
    "description": "It's a lot of heat in the nest"
  },
  {
    "index": 139,
    "question": "The one who often gets 100 points on the test...",
    "answer": "Paper",
    "description": "The 100 is on paper, isn't it?"
  },
  {
    "index": 140,
    "question": "It's not dry because it's still..",
    "answer": "Vibrate",
    "description": "Yes, the phone doesn't ring, that's why it vibrates..."
  },
  {
    "index": 141,
    "question": "Andi has ten apples",
    "answer": "Ten",
    "description": "The stingy andi really doesn't want to give the apple"
  },
  {
    "index": 142,
    "question": "Who can catch criminals at night..",
    "answer": "Proud",
    "description": "Proud to be able to catch criminals, aren't you?"
  },
  {
    "index": 143,
    "question": "Naive vocalist……",
    "answer": "A little",
    "description": "As far as I know, it's only David, right?"
  },
  {
    "index": 144,
    "question": "Eating ketoprak with gado gado is not delicious without...",
    "answer": "Ketelen",
    "description": "Because if you don't drink it, you can't taste it"
  },
  {
    "index": 145,
    "question": "An animal that has nine lives is",
    "answer": "Impossible",
    "description": "Because every living thing has only one life"
  },
  {
    "index": 146,
    "question": "Indonesian staple food from ancient times",
    "answer": "Stale",
    "description": "That's stale... people from the past"
  },
  {
    "index": 147,
    "question": "Nothing .... cracked",
    "answer": "Shard",
    "description": "The glass must be cracked."
  },
  {
    "index": 148,
    "question": "Usually people take pills because...",
    "answer": "Remember",
    "description": "Vitamins can be medicinal"
  },
  {
    "index": 149,
    "question": "rice comes from ?",
    "answer": "Earth",
    "description": "Rice comes from the earth, right?"
  },
  {
    "index": 150,
    "question": "How to quit smoking is?",
    "answer": "Swim",
    "description": "Try it if you don't believe me"
  },
  {
    "index": 151,
    "question": "Father doesn't want to eat rice anymore because",
    "answer": "Eat",
    "description": "When the rice is eaten, it is full"
  },
  {
    "index": 152,
    "question": "After eight",
    "answer": "Constipation",
    "description": "Lots of vegetables for smooth digestion"
  },
  {
    "index": 153,
    "question": "If you want to speak English",
    "answer": "Kles",
    "description": "Yes, you have to read if you don't read it, you can't do it!"
  },
  {
    "index": 154,
    "question": "Valentino rosi is a racer from",
    "answer": "mother",
    "description": "If not from his mother from who"
  },
  {
    "index": 155,
    "question": "Road over the river to cross the river..",
    "answer": "Reckless",
    "description": "Cook your way over the river, why don't you take the bridge..."
  },
  {
    "index": 156,
    "question": "The candle flame goes out if the glass is covered because it is lacking",
    "answer": "Work",
    "description": "The candles are already on why are you turning them off"
  },
  {
    "index": 157,
    "question": "Singing in English?",
    "answer": "Rihanna",
    "description": "Have you ever seen Rihana sing Indonesian?"
  },
  {
    "index": 158,
    "question": "The table has legs ...",
    "answer": "Sure",
    "description": "Does a table have legs?"
  },
  {
    "index": 159,
    "question": "Cristiano ronaldo is from?",
    "answer": "Papama",
    "description": "That's right, cr. ronaldo comes from papa and mama"
  },
  {
    "index": 160,
    "question": "What's a big belly in Chinese?",
    "answer": "Chachingan",
    "description": "Because if you have a distended stomach, there are worms"
  },
  {
    "index": 161,
    "question": "One chicken has 2 legs… a 2-legged chicken is there???",
    "answer": "One",
    "description": "Focus please focus"
  },
  {
    "index": 162,
    "question": "Drinks that can withstand sleepiness and are delicious when you usually stay up late",
    "answer": "Again",
    "description": "Would you like to add more if you like it"
  },
  {
    "index": 163,
    "question": "People living next door to the house are usually called...",
    "answer": "Rangga",
    "description": "Yes it's my neighbor"
  },
  {
    "index": 164,
    "question": "Name of the bridge between Surabaya and Madura",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "description": "Indeed, the Suramadu Bridge already exists"
  },
  {
    "index": 165,
    "question": "Mamat was scolded by the teacher because… school",
    "answer": "Break",
    "description": "If you skip school you will be scolded"
  },
  {
    "index": 166,
    "question": "If thirsty drink",
    "answer": "Hold",
    "description": "It's not break time yet, the boss will be scolded later, can be fired.."
  },
  {
    "index": 167,
    "question": "The motor usually leaks at?",
    "answer": "The tires",
    "description": "The motorcycle has a leak in the tire"
  },
  {
    "index": 168,
    "question": "Don't know that's why you don't",
    "answer": "You know",
    "description": "If you don't know him, you don't know who he is"
  },
  {
    "index": 169,
    "question": "Similar and difficult to distinguish because of children...",
    "answer": "Komodo",
    "description": "Because Komodo dragons are hard to tell"
  },
  {
    "index": 170,
    "question": "Before Monday is the day..",
    "answer": "Holiday",
    "description": "Who said wrong??"
  },
  {
    "index": 171,
    "question": "Where is the place of birth of i gusti ngurah rai?",
    "answer": "Earth",
    "description": "Indonesia is still on earth right?"
  },
  {
    "index": 172,
    "question": "From bandung to surabaya we use ...",
    "answer": "Pants",
    "description": "When you go from Bandung to Surabaya, you don't wear pants.. shame"
  },
  {
    "index": 173,
    "question": "A guy who likes to smile and smile alone is a sign...",
    "answer": "Crazy",
    "description": "It's a common symptom"
  },
  {
    "index": 174,
    "question": "You came late then you",
    "answer": "Congratulations",
    "description": "It's arrived"
  },
  {
    "index": 175,
    "question": "Is there any sugar?",
    "answer": "Glass",
    "description": "If it's not in the glass, ants eat it"
  },
  {
    "index": 176,
    "question": "Usually people die in?",
    "answer": "Tell me",
    "description": "Tell relatives… recently buried"
  },
  {
    "index": 177,
    "question": "As clever as a squirrel jumps, it will...too",
    "answer": "Way",
    "description": "Cook squirrels can't walk, are you tired..."
  },
  {
    "index": 178,
    "question": "A musical instrument that is played by swiping...",
    "answer": "Berets",
    "description": "Don't swipe it, you'll get scratched. It's expensive, you know."
  },
  {
    "index": 179,
    "question": "What person is hacked doesn't work?",
    "answer": "People don't get it",
    "description": "Well, that's why it doesn't work, right?"
  },
  {
    "index": 180,
    "question": "Bigger ____ than the pole",
    "answer": "Market",
    "description": "It's true that the market is bigger than a pole.."
  },
  {
    "index": 181,
    "question": "Far in the eyes near at ..",
    "answer": "Here",
    "description": "If you look far away, stay here close"
  },
  {
    "index": 182,
    "question": "Horse with legs...",
    "answer": "Sure",
    "description": "Horses do have legs"
  },
  {
    "index": 183,
    "question": "My mother went to the house of Mrs. because",
    "answer": "Shit",
    "description": "Mom mothers go to the house of the housewife usually to eat out to save money at home"
  },
  {
    "index": 184,
    "question": "Can be drawn but can't be seen",
    "answer": "Ears",
    "description": "Please try..."
  },
  {
    "index": 185,
    "question": "In biology",
    "answer": "Son",
    "description": "If not the child then who"
  },
  {
    "index": 186,
    "question": "removing armpit hair",
    "answer": "Me",
    "description": "It's someone else's time that I took out"
  },
  {
    "index": 187,
    "question": "Wake up I keep ...",
    "answer": "literate",
    "description": "Be sure to wake up and open your eyes first"
  },
  {
    "index": 188,
    "question": "Can sms if there is...",
    "answer": "Hplah",
    "description": "If you don't have a cellphone where can you text"
  },
  {
    "index": 189,
    "question": "What do you do before going to the mosque?",
    "answer": "Parking",
    "description": "Never mind motorbikes… sandals can't go in…"
  },
  {
    "index": 190,
    "question": "Lizards like to eat",
    "answer": "Many",
    "description": "You don't always add"
  },
  {
    "index": 191,
    "question": "When passing s1",
    "answer": "Size",
    "description": "Size, can pass undergraduate.."
  },
  {
    "index": 192,
    "question": "Don't watch football",
    "answer": "Gajuga",
    "description": "As long as there is coffee, it's fine"
  },
  {
    "index": 193,
    "question": "When people sleep usually...",
    "answer": "Better",
    "description": "Yeah, so it's better not to sleep anymore.."
  },
  {
    "index": 194,
    "question": "The pillow is turned over so...",
    "answer": "Cold",
    "description": "If you don't believe me, try it"
  },
  {
    "index": 195,
    "question": "Vehicles starting with the letter b ?",
    "answer": "Car",
    "description": "Vehicles starting with (i) b, yes cars ..."
  },
  {
    "index": 196,
    "question": "The leader of a village is usually called sir",
    "answer": "No",
    "description": "If you are called, you must turn around"
  },
  {
    "index": 197,
    "question": "There is a father",
    "answer": "Calculate",
    "description": "So that nothing is left behind"
  },
  {
    "index": 198,
    "question": "Which is usually on the beach?",
    "answer": "lips",
    "description": "The beach is called the shoreline"
  },
  {
    "index": 199,
    "question": "Sit the same low",
    "answer": "foot",
    "description": "It's hard to know if it's the same hand!"
  },
  {
    "index": 200,
    "question": "When someone is given a birthday...",
    "answer": "Yani",
    "description": "Because people with birthdays will surely age less"
  },
  {
    "index": 201,
    "question": "Play tennis using",
    "answer": "Jacket",
    "description": "Because the weather is cold"
  },
  {
    "index": 202,
    "question": "When the child comes home late at night, the parents must be..",
    "answer": "Know the time",
    "description": "If you don't know the time, the child will come home at night, it will be considered noon"
  },
  {
    "index": 203,
    "question": "Bandung ocean ?",
    "answer": "Water",
    "description": "Because of the water in the sea"
  },
  {
    "index": 204,
    "question": "To be safe, road cars must exist...",
    "answer": "we",
    "description": "If the car runs without us, it's called rolling"
  },
  {
    "index": 205,
    "question": "Bird animal that can?",
    "answer": "Dude",
    "description": "If you fly together with friends, right?"
  },
  {
    "index": 206,
    "question": "To clean we bathe with",
    "answer": "Sure",
    "description": "If you're not sure, don't shower"
  },
  {
    "index": 207,
    "question": "There must be fire...",
    "answer": "Anya",
    "description": "Yes there is an a, if there is no a it becomes pi dong"
  },
  {
    "index": 208,
    "question": "Lieonel messi plays football in",
    "answer": "Bear",
    "description": "So much more..."
  },
  {
    "index": 209,
    "question": "Food tastes bland",
    "answer": "Suggestion",
    "description": "Give advice to the cook, hopefully next time it will be better"
  },
  {
    "index": 210,
    "question": "Fasting in the month?",
    "answer": "distant",
    "description": "Fasting on earth is not good enough, pretending to fast on the moon"
  },
  {
    "index": 211,
    "question": "What leaves can you eat?",
    "answer": "Daunat",
    "description": "It's delicious to eat, especially the chocolate taste"
  },
  {
    "index": 212,
    "question": "Long distance running..",
    "answer": "Leave",
    "description": "If you're close, you won't run away,"
  },
  {
    "index": 213,
    "question": "Letters?",
    "answer": "Abdxt",
    "description": "Those are all letters, right?"
  },
  {
    "index": 214,
    "question": "When bathing people usually rub...",
    "answer": "Cheek",
    "description": "You're going to be cute! Isn't that right?"
  },
  {
    "index": 215,
    "question": "It's almost hard",
    "answer": "Nose",
    "description": "Hey, do you like picking your nose too?"
  },
  {
    "index": 216,
    "question": "Very delicious vegetables",
    "answer": "Ludes",
    "description": "Delicious vegetables sell out fast"
  },
  {
    "index": 217,
    "question": "Resolve congestion with?",
    "answer": "Lubricants",
    "description": "Just try to get your fence stuck with a lubricant! It'll be fine"
  },
  {
    "index": 218,
    "question": "Sounds of jreeng musical instruments",
    "answer": "Vibrate",
    "description": "Pas jreeeng... the guitar vibrates..."
  },
  {
    "index": 219,
    "question": "Call not seen",
    "answer": "Rhino",
    "description": "Try calling you won't see it"
  },
  {
    "index": 220,
    "question": "What are elementary school children most afraid of?",
    "answer": "Injected",
    "description": "Anyone who likes injections?!"
  },
  {
    "index": 221,
    "question": "Jakarta usually...",
    "answer": "Platb",
    "description": "Because Jakarta has plate number B, it's usually hot"
  },
  {
    "index": 222,
    "question": "Country with many windmills in...",
    "answer": "Petaada",
    "description": "Isn't that right?"
  },
  {
    "index": 223,
    "question": "What do you do when you enter school?",
    "answer": "Ask",
    "description": "Ugh, kids."
  },
  {
    "index": 224,
    "question": "Before becoming rice?",
    "answer": "Hard",
    "description": "Rice is soft, before it's soft, isn't it hard?"
  },
  {
    "index": 225,
    "question": "The farmer is planting rice paddy",
    "answer": "Pass",
    "description": "Pa' Didi is going to the market it seems"
  },
  {
    "index": 226,
    "question": "Cigarettes when burned give off",
    "answer": "Child",
    "description": "Cigarettes in front of children are not good, so first take them out of the smoking room"
  },
  {
    "index": 227,
    "question": "What happens when the cat is on the tree down first?",
    "answer": "The intention",
    "description": "If there's a will there's a way!"
  },
  {
    "index": 228,
    "question": "Washing dishes must be with ...",
    "answer": "Aware",
    "description": "If you don't realize it, the plate won't be washed, it will break..."
  },
  {
    "index": 229,
    "question": "Rose met her boyfriend that night at...",
    "answer": "Angry",
    "description": "Grandma says it's not nice"
  },
  {
    "index": 230,
    "question": "A representative of the people can go to Senayan by using the route..",
    "answer": "Viatol",
    "description": "Well, exit the toll road at Semanggi, until it's Senayan.."
  },
  {
    "index": 231,
    "question": "What is the difference between a motorbike and a bicycle",
    "answer": "Obviously",
    "description": "You know the difference between thinking and thinking"
  },
  {
    "index": 232,
    "question": "Tooth stuck in?",
    "answer": "foot",
    "description": "Take a motorbike to change gears on the foot"
  },
  {
    "index": 233,
    "question": "River in Kalimantan",
    "answer": "Many",
    "description": "There is a Barito River, a Kapuas River, a Kahayan River, etc."
  },
  {
    "index": 234,
    "question": "Fish breathe by...",
    "answer": "Permission",
    "description": "If not allowed can't breathe"
  },
  {
    "index": 235,
    "question": "Food is spicy because...",
    "answer": "Manya",
    "description": "Kare is his name, if he's a bitch, his name is curry"
  },
  {
    "index": 236,
    "question": "Usually on the side of the road",
    "answer": "Strike out",
    "description": "That's a sign no parking is allowed"
  },
  {
    "index": 237,
    "question": "A good mother should be...",
    "answer": "Our Mother",
    "description": "Never be reciprocated"
  },
  {
    "index": 238,
    "question": "Effective medicine for low blood pressure?",
    "answer": "Spit",
    "description": "If someone with low blood is spit out, they will have high blood immediately"
  },
  {
    "index": 239,
    "question": "The one the boxer hits",
    "answer": "Relax",
    "description": "Those who hit each other boxers we saw were relaxed"
  },
  {
    "index": 240,
    "question": "What kind of cilok can make a baby happy",
    "answer": "Chilokba",
    "description": "Cilook baaa ih so lousy…."
  },
  {
    "index": 241,
    "question": "wind instruments",
    "answer": "Difficult",
    "description": "It's hard to play the flute"
  },
  {
    "index": 242,
    "question": "Not magic",
    "answer": "Magic",
    "description": "If it's not magic, it means it's not magic"
  },
  {
    "index": 243,
    "question": "Astronauts going out?",
    "answer": "Ganyari",
    "description": "If an astronaut goes his family will look for him"
  },
  {
    "index": 244,
    "question": "Where we can see the s in the middle",
    "answer": "Mattress",
    "description": "Yeah yeah that's the middle s right?"
  },
  {
    "index": 245,
    "question": "Which sandal is the best?",
    "answer": "Sandalters",
    "description": "Well if this is swaya I also like it!"
  },
  {
    "index": 246,
    "question": "People can stand with",
    "answer": "Strong",
    "description": "If you can't stand how can you stand"
  },
  {
    "index": 247,
    "question": "What lies at the end of the sea",
    "answer": "Letters",
    "description": "Because the word sea ends in the letter t, that's easy"
  },
  {
    "index": 248,
    "question": "Glass _ _ _ _ _ . is usually there on the streets.",
    "answer": "Nigjo",
    "description": "Protest minus 50"
  },
  {
    "index": 249,
    "question": "A person with two bodies?",
    "answer": "Great",
    "description": "If you see a person with two bodies, it will make a scene"
  },
  {
    "index": 250,
    "question": "People draw water in...",
    "answer": "Pour",
    "description": "After the neem water has to be poured.."
  },
  {
    "index": 251,
    "question": "Open the lock using ...",
    "answer": "Sound",
    "description": "Click as it sounds"
  },
  {
    "index": 252,
    "questions": "Usually stored in sacks",
    "answer": "Free",
    "description": "If you want rice or sand, feel free"
  },
  {
    "index": 253,
    "question": "Bull butting using..??!",
    "answer": "Power",
    "description": "If he doesn't use his strength, he can gore."
  },
  {
    "index": 254,
    "question": "Prison can be noisy if all the prisoners",
    "answer": "Cough",
    "description": "The cough must be contagious, right, it's season"
  },
  {
    "index": 255,
    "question": "What monkeys are stepped on don't complain",
    "answer": "Ceramic",
    "description": "Because it's loud"
  },
  {
    "index": 256,
    "question": "Fence eats...",
    "answer": "Still",
    "description": "Because the fence can't eat"
  },
  {
    "index": 257,
    "question": "When we go to the market we usually meet...",
    "answer": "Neighbor",
    "description": "I often meet my ex..."
  },
  {
    "index": 258,
    "question": "Why do people eat with their right hand?",
    "answer": "Because of the food",
    "description": "If you use your left hand it's called makiri"
  },
  {
    "index": 259,
    "question": "A painter who can only draw rainbows",
    "answer": "Great",
    "description": "Your painter is great.. who the hell.. God's rainbows.."
  },
  {
    "index": 260,
    "question": "The backmost part of the tooth is...",
    "answer": "Drummer",
    "description": "Arand Maulana's band is the last drummer"
  },
  {
    "index": 261,
    "question": "Can you move on your own without being asked?",
    "answer": "collapse",
    "description": "That's called gravity-assisted!"
  },
  {
    "index": 262,
    "question": "Not allowed to enter class",
    "answer": "Fly",
    "description": "Flies disturb students' study"
  },
  {
    "index": 263,
    "question": "The goodness of people can be seen from...",
    "answer": "Son",
    "description": "If the child is well taken care of"
  },
  {
    "index": 264,
    "question": "Signs a romantic guy likes...",
    "answer": "Attention",
    "description": "Wow"
  },
  {
    "index": 265,
    "question": "Everyone breathes through ..?",
    "answer": "Hole",
    "description": "If you don't have a hole in your nose, you'll die"
  },
  {
    "index": 266,
    "question": "Rendang is a food that comes from the city that we usually call?",
    "answer": "Fine",
    "description": "Yeah, we call the city of the desert fluently, right?"
  },
  {
    "index": 267,
    "question": "The one driving the ship is called ...",
    "answer": "Different",
    "description": "Because there were a lot of people at the helm"
  },
  {
    "index": 268,
    "question": "If bitten by a spider, it could be...",
    "answer": "Pain",
    "description": "Remember, this is not a comic world"
  },
  {
    "index": 269,
    "question": "What do you do when the car is running?",
    "answer": "The song",
    "description": "So you don't get bored driving right?!"
  },
  {
    "index": 270,
    "question": "Name an example of an animal that walks slowly...",
    "answer": "Wolf",
    "description": "Wolves run fast, walking slow..."
  },
  {
    "index": 271,
    "question": "Poultry with two legs is",
    "answer": "Correct",
    "description": "Really?"
  },
  {
    "index": 272,
    "question": "Slipped musical instrument",
    "answer": "Berets",
    "description": "Ugh, if you swipe it, it's a beret, isn't it, honey?"
  },
  {
    "index": 273,
    "About": "No matter how fierce a tiger is, it won't eat...",
    "answer": "Avocados",
    "description": "Yes tigers love avocado"
  },
  {
    "index": 274,
    "question": "When we go upstream, we swim to ?",
    "answer": "Keair",
    "description": "If you swim, you're definitely in the water"
  },
  {
    "index": 275,
    "question": "People who work in hospitals ?",
    "answer": "Salary",
    "description": "His name also works.. yes it must be paid"
  },
  {
    "index": 276,
    "question": "If we don't wear a helmet we get hit",
    "answer": "Papa",
    "description": "The opposite is okay, why is it, why is it fine, for example"
  },
  {
    "index": 277,
    "question": "Wake up I keep ..",
    "answer": "literate",
    "description": "Be literate before taking a shower..as soon as..."
  },
  {
    "index": 278,
    "question": "Who regulates the football match??",
    "answer": "Time",
    "description": "The rule is 2×45 minutes..normally.."
  },
  {
    "index": 279,
    "question": "3-wheeled vehicle?",
    "answer": "Fair",
    "description": "There are bemo, bajaj, rickshaw and others..."
  },
  {
    "index": 280,
    "question": "Indonesian eat",
    "wrong answer",
    "description": "Eat is in English, not Indonesian"
  },
  {
    "index": 281,
    "question": "The car can't run because of the tires...",
    "answer": "you",
    "description": "If there are many(k) people, you can't pass, right?"
  },
  {
    "index": 282,
    "question": "If a goat is stabbed, it will be burned?",
    "answer": "Run",
    "description": "What's wrong with the goat, until it was stabbed or burned "
  },
  {
    "index": 283,
    "question": "Water rippled no ...",
    "answer": "Care",
    "description": "If it's calm it's calm, it's not rippling or noisy."
  },
  {
    "index": 284,
    "question": "That romantic gift for you...",
    "answer": "Applied",
    "description": "Congratulations"
  },
  {
    "index": 285,
    "question": "Delicious Padang cuisine",
    "answer": "kick",
    "description": "Because good food tastes great"
  },
  {
    "index": 286,
    "question": "To turn on the light we have to press...",
    "answer": "Once",
    "description": "Twice you die right?"
  },
  {
    "index": 287,
    "question": "If you drink at ?",
    "answer": "Swallow",
    "description": "When sprayed by the shaman"
  },
  {
    "index": 288,
    "question": "stringed instrument...",
    "answer": "Sound",
    "description": "There is a violin, cello, fiddle and more"
  },
  {
    "index": 289,
    "question": "Buy medicine at",
    "answer": "Drink",
    "description": "Because if you don't drink it, what else do you do"
  },
  {
    "index": 290,
    "question": "The most beautiful road in Bandung is the ...",
    "answer": "With you",
    "description": "Wow that's beautiful"
  },
  {
    "index": 291,
    "question": "Car parked at",
    "answer": "Turn off",
    "description": "If you don't turn off the car will run"
  },
  {
    "index": 292,
    "question": "Youth gets a boyfriend because he likes to play...",
    "answer": "Eyes",
    "description": "As long as you don't flirt with other people's girlfriends…."
  },
  {
    "index": 293,
    "question": "I have five balloons",
    "answer": "Duaar",
    "description": "popping balloons, my heart is so messed up sob sob…"
  },
  {
    "index": 294,
    "question": "Fight mom",
    "answer": "Sin",
    "description": "If you are afraid of sin, don't go against the word mama"
  },
  {
    "index": 295,
    "question": "A contest winner usually gets",
    "answer": "Ridho",
    "description": "If you don't get the approval of your parents, you won't win"
  },
  {
    "index": 296,
    "question": "Everything will be beautiful on...",
    "answer": "No",
    "description": "Not everything ends well tho.."
  },
  {
    "index": 297,
    "question": "Animals have 6 fingers",
    "answer": "Funny",
    "description": "Yeah it's cute if you have 6 fingers"
  },
  {
    "index": 298,
    "question": "What is the strangest animal",
    "answer": "Butterfly",
    "description": "Because during the day eat rice, at night drink milk"
  },
  {
    "index": 299,
    "question": "The frog's child is called...",
    "answer": "Family",
    "description": "There is a mother, yes, there is a child."
  },
  {
    "index": 300,
    "question": "Water rippled no sign?",
    "answer": "Flat",
    "description": "If it rippled it would be wavy"
  },
  {
    "index": 301,
    "question": "What box can't be moved",
    "answer": "Penalty",
    "description": "Try it if you can"
  },
  {
    "index": 302,
    "question": "Apple tastes",
    "answer": "Tired",
    "description": "If you have to get tired, you have to stand up"
  },
  {
    "index": 303,
    "question": "In the sea there are anchovy whales and fish..",
    "answer": "Cob",
    "description": "And much more"
  },
  {
    "index": 304,
    "question": "People eat because?",
    "answer": "Aware",
    "description": "If you don't know you can't eat"
  },
  {
    "index": 305,
    "question": "We can see our own face in..",
    "answer": "Sima",
    "description": "There's a photo of us in sim a, right?"
  },
  {
    "index": 306,
    "question": "Location of the 7 wonders of the world….",
    "answer": "Search",
    "description": "Borobudur is in Jogja, India has the Taj Mahal, and many others"
  },
  {
    "index": 307,
    "question": "The person who leads the country",
    "answer": "Absolutely not",
    "description": "There must be people who lead the country"
  },
  {
    "index": 308,
    "question": "When an ambulance passes, it usually makes a sound",
    "answer": "Tintin",
    "description": "If an ambulance passes by a crowded place, it will honk"
  },
  {
    "index": 309,
    "question": "Scorpions and snakes live..",
    "answer": "Both",
    "description": "I mentioned a scorpion and a snake that's why it's both"
  },
  {
    "index": 310,
    "question": "Dare because it's right ___ because it's wrong",
    "answer": "No",
    "description": "Wahaha easy right??"
  },
  {
    "index": 311,
    "question": "In a football match",
    "answer": "See",
    "description": "If he can't see why is he guarding the goal?!"
  },
  {
    "index": 312,
    "question": "Turtles are animals that have...",
    "answer": "girlfriend",
    "description": "It's okay to have a girl friend, don't be so possessive, please.."
  },
  {
    "index": 313,
    "question": "A football player who is rarely ignored by opponents...",
    "answer": "trivial",
    "description": "How can you ignore it, it's really trivial..."
  },
  {
    "index": 314,
    "question": "In order to perform optimally a singer must check...",
    "answer": "Balance",
    "description": "So that there is no burden to sing, you have already paid for it."
  },
  {
    "index": 315,
    "question": "Far in the eyes near at",
    "answer": "Here",
    "description": "If it's far away, stay here"
  },
  {
    "index": 316,
    "question": "Fast motorbike or bicycle",
    "answer": "Car",
    "description": "Yes it's definitely a faster car"
  },
  {
    "index": 317,
    "question": "Ring is worn on the finger",
    "answer": "Enter",
    "description": "Yes, if you don't log in you can't use it"
  },
  {
    "index": 318,
    "question": "What we wear when it rains...",
    "answer": "Honey",
    "description": "If it's wet, it's a shame it's wet because it's wet"
  },
  {
    "index": 319,
    "question": "Animal stuck to the wall?",
    "answer": "Tired",
    "description": "Just walking is tired, let alone sticking..."
  },
  {
    "index": 320,
    "question": "If you were surrounded by 20 lions what would you do?",
    "answer": "Relax",
    "description": "It's just the tail"
  },
  {
    "index": 321,
    "question": "People are cold",
    "answer": "Remotac",
    "description": "Ac temperature in remote is 16°c, cat is cold."
  },
  {
    "index": 322,
    "question": "Upin's friend??",
    "answer": "Ijat",
    "description": "Because of his sister's ipin"
  },
  {
    "index": 323,
    "question": "Farmers hoe to ?",
    "answer": "Down",
    "description": "Is there really a hoe up"
  },
  {
    "index": 324,
    "question": "Elephant only in",
    "answer": "Back",
    "description": "Because the elephant has the letter h on the back"
  },
  {
    "index": 325,
    "problem": "In physics, solids turning into liquids are called processes.",
    "answer": "Pawnshop",
    "description": "Need quick funds? 30 minutes immediately disbursed!"
  },
  {
    "index": 326,
    "question": "Ani draws the same triangle",
    "answer": "Kiki",
    "description": "Because it's group work"
  },
  {
    "index": 327,
    "question": "Not voting at election",
    "answer": "Shit",
    "description": "Election determines the fate of the nation, not voting is not fun"
  },
  {
    "index": 328,
    "question": "Legs are hot from being hit",
    "answer": "Lopot",
    "description": "Hot with exhaust"
  },
  {
    "index": 329,
    "question": "Thieves usually steal in...",
    "answer": "Silence",
    "description": "If you make noise you'll find out"
  },
  {
    "index": 330,
    "question": "Police set the road then .....",
    "answer": "Fine",
    "description": "After managing the road, it's fine"
  },
  {
    "index": 331,
    "question": "A little - a little long so...",
    "answer": "Many",
    "description": "A little if you add more, you get a lot"
  },
  {
    "index": 332,
    "question": "……..behind the stone",
    "answer": "Uutab",
    "description": "That's right, if the uutab is behind it turns to stone"
  },
  {
    "index": 333,
    "question": "There are ants there",
    "answer": "Enya",
    "description": "If there's no e, it's smut"
  },
  {
    "index": 334,
    "question": "A person who rarely goes anywhere is called?",
    "answer": "Goalkeeper",
    "description": "Well if you're conceding everywhere, dong!"
  },
  {
    "index": 335,
    "question": "The world is not as wide as a leaf??",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "description": "Because the world isn't as wide as a leaf"
  },
  {
    "index": 336,
    "question": "Abbreviation of land",
    "answer": "Sda",
    "description": "That's right! land, air, and water are natural resources"
  },
  {
    "index": 337,
    "question": "Grass-eating animals",
    "answer": "Poor",
    "description": "It's a pity that you have eaten grass as satay again."
  },
  {
    "index": 338,
    "question": "What's the fast motor?",
    "answer": "The bolt",
    "description": "If the body doesn't tighten, how will it come off?"
  },
  {
    "index": 339,
    "question": "Vehicle pulled by horse..",
    "answer": "Gaaman",
    "description": "Due to being pulled by a horse the vehicle could have an accident"
  },
  {
    "index": 340,
    "question": "Tarzan's friend..",
    "answer": "You",
    "description": "You look like an ape, me too..."
  },
  {
    "index": 341,
    "question": "What did father do during the month of Ramadan",
    "answer": "Work",
    "description": "Because it's not time for vacation yet"
  },
  {
    "index": 342,
    "question": "Before God created nature. God created?",
    "answer": "Vetyvera",
    "description": "Vetyvera is nature's sister, come first, okay?"
  },
  {
    "index": 343,
    "question": "Living things that have a supply of water",
    "answer": "Camel",
    "description": "…"
  },
  {
    "index": 344,
    "question": "20 divided by 2 is calculated...",
    "answer": "Alms",
    "description": "Does 20 divided by 2 count as alms"
  },
  {
    "index": 345,
    "question": "Elephant dead leave ..",
    "answer": "Dangnya",
    "description": "Stay-the cage, if in the forest leave the forest.."
  },
  {
    "index": 346,
    "question": "Galang keeps books in...",
    "answer": "Ma'am",
    "description": "The book was borrowed by Galang yesterday afternoon"
  },
  {
    "index": 347,
    "question": "Items that can be borrowed",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "description": "If you don't have it, you can't borrow it"
  },
  {
    "index": 348,
    "question": "Lizards usually eat?",
    "answer": "Yummm",
    "description": "That's how it sounds"
  },
  {
    "index": 349,
    "question": "Rain is falling from...",
    "answer": "Maghrib",
    "description": "Because Asr hasn't come down yet"
  },
  {
    "index": 350,
    "question": "Will the flute be blown?",
    "answer": "Wet",
    "description": "Just hold on to your flute when it's blown out..."
  },
  {
    "index": 351,
    "question": "Most people sleep time",
    "answer": "Break",
    "description": "If you don't brake, you don't sleep"
  },
  {
    "index": 352,
    "question": "Egg or chicken first",
    "answer": "Adam",
    "description": "Because the prophet Adam was in the world before the chicken and the egg"
  },
  {
    "index": 353,
    "question": "Sunday is also called a date?",
    "answer": "No",
    "description": "If the day is the day, if the date is the date"
  },
  {
    "index": 354,
    "question": "When fighting soldiers bring..",
    "answer": "Shoes",
    "description": "If you squeeze your foot it hurts..."
  },
  {
    "index": 355,
    "question": "A chicken is called ...",
    "answer": "Full",
    "description": "Yes, eating chicken makes you full"
  },
  {
    "index": 356,
    "question": "Bring a car must bring",
    "answer": "One",
    "description": "If you bring two, how about trying ..?!?!"
  },
  {
    "index": 357,
    "question": "End of ..... sepah thrown away",
    "answer": "Eat",
    "description": "Yes.. if you eat it, throw it away"
  },
  {
    "index": 358,
    "question": "Motorcycle has wheels",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "description": "Obviously a motorbike has wheels if you don't have one it can't run"
  },
  {
    "index": 359,
    "question": "The wheel is always...",
    "answer": "Color",
    "description": "There is no wheel without color"
  },
  {
    "index": 360,
    "question": "On the highway there are usually...",
    "answer": "Lights",
    "description": "If you don't have a light, you won't see it."
  },
  {
    "index": 361,
    "question": "In addition to tug of war, people celebrate the 17s with?",
    "answer": "Pray a prayer",
    "description": "Because it's a blessing"
  },
  {
    "index": 362,
    "question": "stringed instrument",
    "answer": "normal",
    "description": "Because it is common in the market"
  },
  {
    "index": 363,
    "question": "The coffee shop is called...",
    "answer": "Times",
    "description": "Hohoho, it's good to have coffee on the side of the river in the afternoon.."
  },
  {
    "index": 364,
    "question": "Camels live in...",
    "answer": "Nature",
    "description": "Indeed all living things live in nature"
  },
  {
    "index": 365,
    "question": "What is the name for a person who has taken then gone",
    "answer": "Former",
    "description": "Because your ex is a thief who hurts your heart and then leaves"
  },
  {
    "index": 366,
    "question": "rice is ready",
    "answer": "Thanks",
    "description": "If the rice is ready, you should be grateful"
  },
  {
    "index": 367,
    "questions": "What students often take to see are read",
    "answer": "Babv",
    "description": "Chapter five is in every textbook"
  },
  {
    "index": 368,
    "question": "Sir rt can fly",
    "answer": "Ticket",
    "description": "If you want to fly by plane you must have a ticket"
  },
  {
    "index": 369,
    "question": "What do you do when you drink coffee?",
    "answer": "Sruput",
    "description": "Let's make it taste more coffee, won't it!"
  },
  {
    "index": 370,
    "question": "On the last lap rossi cut the marquest for sure...",
    "answer": "Kungan",
    "description": "Rossi is the best around the corner ."
  },
  {
    "index": 371,
    "question": "Prambanan temple is a relic of the era..",
    "answer": "In the past",
    "description": "No one builds temples anymore, right?"
  },
  {
    "index": 372,
    "question": "Children are not attending school because...",
    "answer": "Out",
    "description": "If he's in the palace it means he's in school"
  },
  {
    "index": 373,
    "question": "The friend who helped batman against 50 enemies was?",
    "answer": "Hassle",
    "description": "It's a hassle 50 enemies….ouch.."
  },
  {
    "index": 374,
    "question": "The merlion statue is in",
    "answer": "The place",
    "description": "That's where it is, when the statues go for a walk"
  },
  {
    "index": 375,
    "question": "Fish breathe with",
    "answer": "Relax",
    "description": "If you stumble you can die"
  },
  {
    "index": 376,
    "question": "The motorbike fell because",
    "answer": "Galiat",
    "description": "Because in front of him there was a dig, he dug.. he fell"
  },
  {
    "index": 377,
    "question": "People die from loss...",
    "answer": "Breath",
    "description": "Time of the dead breath"
  },
  {
    "index": 378,
    "question": "If the ant is small",
    "answer": "Animals",
    "description": "I'm not wrong, am I?"
  },
  {
    "index": 379,
    "question": "The flag of this color is ...",
    "answer": "Just two",
    "description": "When is the color three?"
  },
  {
    "index": 380,
    "question": "Real madrid player number 11",
    "answer": "Bule",
    "description": "Gareth Bale is indeed a Caucasian. Why is that so hard?"
  },
  {
    "index": 381,
    "question": "There is a king",
    "answer": "Orphan",
    "description": "My father died "
  },
  {
    "index": 382,
    "question": "Tea is made with ice",
    "answer": "Fresh",
    "description": "Especially in hot weather"
  },
  {
    "index": 383,
    "question": "We see the stars in...",
    "answer": "shoulder",
    "description": "It's on the shoulders of a general, that's the rank you know..."
  },
  {
    "index": 384,
    "question": "Foot stepped on glass...",
    "answer": "Eyes",
    "description": "Well can't see…broken glasses…"
  },
  {
    "index": 385,
    "question": "Can you be strong enough to eat spinach?",
    "answer": "Toploe",
    "description": "It's really top, I'm just lazy when it's just spinach"
  },
  {
    "index": 386,
    "question": "Amazing behavior",
    "answer": "Whistling",
    "description": "I'm surprised."
  },
  {
    "index": 387,
    "question": "How to add friends in an instant",
    "answer": "Nembakgirl",
    "description": "If you get rejected, you'll just say we're friends..poor"
  },
  {
    "index": 388,
    "question": "What often annoys people when they want to do good?",
    "answer": "Naughty",
    "description": "Why do you want to be bothered by doing good? You're so naughty"
  },
  {
    "index": 389,
    "question": "If you want to go to a wedding",
    "answer": "Anrap",
    "description": "That's right, it's neat and handsome"
  },
  {
    "index": 390,
    "question": "Trees that grow after the fasting month",
    "answer": "Sorry",
    "description": "Apologies for the inner birth yes"
  },
  {
    "index": 391,
    "question": "There are eleven sheep in the truck",
    "answer": "Eleven",
    "description": "You just jump, don't run away"
  },
  {
    "index": 392,
    "question": "Freeway traffic",
    "answer": "Top",
    "description": "Means the toll road must be top"
  },
  {
    "index": 393,
    "question": "The one that helps the doctor...",
    "answer": "Heal",
    "description": "Those who help the doctor, God willing, get well..."
  },
  {
    "index": 394,
    "question": "Beach in Jakarta?",
    "answer": "Abyss",
    "description": "So long gone from waste, sad"
  },
  {
    "index": 395,
    "question": "An animal that can change its skin color",
    "answer": "Advanced",
    "description": "(chameleon) because animals that can change color are sophisticated, right!"
  },
  {
    "index": 396,
    "question": "What do thieves usually do on Saturday nights, Sundays",
    "answer": "Clean",
    "description": "Because the clothes smell bad, because people chased people on Friday night Saturday night"
  },
  {
    "index": 397,
    "question": "Animals that perch on food",
    "answer": "Hungry",
    "description": "It's because I'm hungry"
  },
  {
    "index": 398,
    "question": "United we stand, divided we...",
    "answer": "Split",
    "description": "If you are divorced, you must be separated"
  },
  {
    "index": 399,
    "question": "Jakarta's traffic jams….passing by",
    "answer": "Aplo",
    "description": "Jakarta is jammed, are you ready to pass??"
  },
  {
    "index": 400,
    "question": "People who often come to campus",
    "answer": "Alive",
    "description": "Yeah, if you're dead you can't go to campus"
  },
  {
    "index": 401,
    "question": "In a year…..months",
    "answer": "Only one",
    "description": "Even if you wait five years, the moon is still one."
  },
  {
    "index": 402,
    "question": "After high school graduation",
    "answer": "Home",
    "description": "Going home… tell your parents, congratulations!"
  },
  {
    "index": 403,
    "question": "A deer has..",
    "answer": "Friends",
    "description": "So many friends, so much more..."
  },
  {
    "index": 404,
    "question": "Japanese ninja cartoon",
    "answer": "Watch",
    "description": "Because cartoons are fun"
  },
  {
    "index": 405,
    "question": "Agus wants to play football in...",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "description": "Permitted by his parents, otherwise he will cry"
  },
  {
    "index": 406,
    "question": "What animal is good at predicting the weather",
    "answer": "Tiger",
    "description": "Rain tiger, hot tiger, dark tiger at night."
  },
  {
    "index": 407,
    "question": "What ball looks like a cat?",
    "answer": "Bolaemon",
    "description": "Hi bamboo propeller"
  },
  {
    "index": 408,
    "question": "The one driving the train...",
    "answer": "Masagus",
    "description": "Mas agus is my neighbor, you know..."
  },
  {
    "index": 409,
    "question": "Long distance running",
    "answer": "Unfortunately",
    "description": "It's far, it's not hot yet.."
  },
  {
    "index": 410,
    "question": "Don't forget to sleep when you sleep",
    "answer": "Wake up",
    "description": "If you don't wake up it can be terrible"
  },
  {
    "index": 411,
    "question": "What gorilla is as big as a building?",
    "answer": "Big",
    "description": "Where can there be a gorilla as big as a building…."
  },
  {
    "index": 412,
    "question": "A little bit longer, so...",
    "answer": "A little",
    "description": "It's a little so a little bit is taken"
  },
  {
    "index": 413,
    "question": "The police ticketed the violators with?",
    "answer": "Pririt",
    "description": "If you don't prriiit, don't step aside, the violators"
  }
]
